tackletour.com 2019-06-19

# Tackle News - September 2005

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last Updated:** 2/28/19

Tackletour, LLC is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. 

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes and governs the information collection, use, and sharing practices of Tackletour (the "Website") and its affiliates and divisions as may change from time to time. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Website, and not to information you may provide to any third-party sites to which Tackletour may link to, except as expressly provided herein. This Policy applies regardless of the device used to access Tackletour (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today, or developed in the future). This Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you access or use Tackletour, forum, or the related products, content, activities, features and services available on or through the Website (the "Service(s)"), and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

In this Policy, "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, or any similar identifying information or information associated with the foregoing.

This Policy applies to information we collect on this Website; in email, and other electronic messages between you and this Website; through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website; and when you interact with our advertising and applications on third party websites and services. It does not apply to information collected by any third party application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy or our Terms of Use posted on the Website, which are expressly incorporated herein by reference and made a part of this Policy, your sole remedy is to discontinue your use of the Website and Services. By accessing or using the Website or Services, you agree to this Policy, which may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Website and Services after we make any changes to this Policy is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information in multiple ways, including when you provide information directly to us, and when we passively collect information from you, such as from your browser or device.

-          -User-Provided Information: You may be required to provide personal information to access the forum or use certain parts of the Website or Services. If you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use certain features of the Website or Services.

-          -Emails and Social Media Sites: If you correspond with us by email or via social media, please be aware that when you receive a receipt acknowledging your email, upload to one of our social media pages or accounts, or submission of a form, it means that the message, uploaded item, or form has been routed into the Internet, and not that it has been received by us. Please also note that we may collect information automatically using technology when you visit the Website or social media pages as described in this Policy.

-          -Cookies Information: When you visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the Website. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies. 

-          -Google Analytics: Like many websites we use a tool called "Google Analytics", a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google") to collect information about use of the Website. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve the Website. 

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

-          -To provide the products, services, features, programs, content and information you request.

-          -To operate, maintain, and provide to you the best possible features, products, services, content and functionality of the Website and Services, and overall customer experience.

-          -To analyze visits to the Website and learn about the interests, preferences, demographics and behaviors of our visitors in the aggregate (e.g., across the country) and also on a personal level, so we can improve our products, services and programs and deliver to you the type of content, features, products, services, programs and promotions that you are most interested in.

-          -To process registration requests when you register for our forum.

-          -To prevent, detect or investigate any fraudulent, abusive or illegal act.

-          -In any other way we may describe at or around the time you provide the information.

-          -For any other purpose with your consent.

User Content: Any personal information or content you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Website or Services (for instance, any content you post) (referred to herein as "User Content") becomes available to the public via the Website and our business partners. User Content includes, but is not limited to, forum posts. If you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.

Tackletour reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the Website. Tackletour has the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason including, without limitation, if Tackletour determines in its sole opinion that such information or material violates or may violate any applicable law or our Terms of Use, or to protect or defend Tackletour's rights or property or those of any third party. Tackletour also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.

WHEN WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION

Personally Identifiable Information: Tackletour may disclose and/or share your information between members of Tackletour, and to or with any non-affiliated third parties such as the following:

-          Consent: We may disclose your information to any third parties based on your consent to do so.

-          Service Providers: We may disclose potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to other third parties that provide support services to us such as webhosting, web analytics. We may store personal information in locations that are not under the direct control of Tackletour (for example, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers). These service providers only receive personal information if such information is needed to perform their function(s), and they are not authorized to use any personal information for any other purpose(s).

-          Advertising and Affiliates: Tackletour may allow other companies, called third party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on the Website. These third party ad servers or ad affiliate networks use technology to directly send to your browser the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.

-          Protection of Tackletour and Others: By using the Services, you acknowledge, consent and agree that we may access, preserve and disclose your information, including, but not limited to, any user content, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce our Terms of Service, this Policy, or other contracts with you, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; (d) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Tackletour, its agents and affiliates, its users and/or the public.

-          Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets. User, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions, and you authorize us to disclose your personal information in connection with any such transaction. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution and you authorize us to do so.

-          Public Forum: Our Services offer publicly accessible community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. Please also remember that if you choose to provide information on public features of the Services, individuals reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about what you choose to disclose publicly and make sure it’s information you want to share with the public.

INTERNATIONAL USERS U.S. GOVERNING LAW

The Website is designed for and targets U.S. audiences, and is governed by and operated in accordance with the laws of the United States. We make no representation that the Website and Services are operated in accordance with the laws or regulations of, or governed by, other nations, and we do not warrant or imply that the Website and Services are appropriate for use outside of the United States. By using the Website or Services, you certify that you meet the age and other eligibility requirements set forth in our Terms of Use. If you do not meet such age and other eligibility requirements, please discontinue using the Website and Services immediately, as your continued use indicates that you are agreeing to the collection, use, disclosure, management and storage of your information as described in this Policy.

If you are located outside of the United States, you use the Website and Services at your own risk and initiative, and you are solely responsible for compliance with any applicable local, national and international laws. By using the Website and/or Services and/or providing us with any information, you: (a) consent to the transfer and processing of any information to and within the U.S., (b) acknowledge that U.S. law may provide a lower standard of protection for personal data than the laws of your location and/or residence, and (c) understand that we will collect, transfer, store, process, manage and/or handle your information in accordance with this Policy and U.S. law. Consequently, to the fullest extent permitted by law, you hereby waive any claims relating to the processing of your information in accordance with this Policy that may arise under the laws and regulations of any other country or jurisdiction.

We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use the Website or Services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful, as determined in our sole discretion. Release of your personal information for security purposes to any person or entity under any circumstances, including, without limitation, in connection with any government investigation or litigation, shall be based on a determination made solely by us, exercising our own discretion, permission for which is expressly granted by you to us in accordance with this Policy.

SECURITY

Tackletour uses commercially reasonable ethical, physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. The security of your personal information is important to us, but please remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is ever completely secure. While we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit to the Website or Services, and you do so at your own risk. When Tackletour receives a transmission of personally identifying information from you, Tackletour makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of such information. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our ethical, physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. While we strive to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online.

THIRD PARTY LINKS AND SERVICES

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Website nor the information or content contained therein, and we make no warranty, either express or implied, concerning the content of any such site, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability, or suitability thereof for any particular purpose, nor do we warrant that any such site or its content is free from any claims of copyright, trademark, or other infringement of the rights of third parties, or that any such site or its content is devoid of viruses or other contamination. Tackletour may provide links to other websites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of linked sites does not imply endorsement by Tackletour of any of the linked sites. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Website to another website, our Policy is no longer in effect. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that are linked to the Website, is subject to that other website's own rules and policies. Please read over the other website's rules and policies before proceeding. We do not ensure the security of your personal information if you visit websites not belonging to Tackletour. We further reserve the right to terminate a link to a third party site at any time.

We sometimes use content on the Website or Services that we obtain from third party sites or social media platforms such as Facebook, Instagram, YouTube, and Twitter. The privacy protections provided on these third party sites and social media platforms are not part of our Policy and may differ from the privacy protections described in this Policy. If you upload content on third party sites or social media platforms or sites that share information with the general public, user community, and/or other third party sites, it may be used or shared by us on the Website or our social media pages and accounts to promote our products and services. Consequently, you should review the privacy policies of these third party sites before using them and ensure that you understand how your content may be used.

INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 13 and such children are not permitted to use the Services. If we discover we have received any “personal information” (as defined under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) from a child under the age of 13 in violation of this Policy, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information as quickly as possible. 

CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time to reflect changes in the law, our data collection and use practices, the features of our Services. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Services following the posting of changes to this Policy will mean you accept those changes.
